<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lauren Contreras</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Lauren Contreras</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project Blog Post</title>
      <link>/post/2021/05/09/project-blog-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/05/09/project-blog-post/</guid>
      <description>Link to project 1
Link to google
Introduction I used the HW 6 example for the mosquito weight for the Aedes aegypti species. I chose to upload the vector of mosquito weights onto python, assigning the objects as “females” and “males” accordingly. I also calculated the mean of these weights through python. Next, I reticulated this vector into R. I then had to converted the python objects into numeric R objects since I believe the orginial object were being interpreted as factors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015/07/23/hello-r-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015/07/23/hello-r-markdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction For my first dataset, I gathered information logged by my iPhone under the pre-installed app “Health”. My daily steps, walking distance, and flights climbed are automatically logged and saved through my mobile device. Since I carry my phone everywhere I go, this is a reliable source of data. This information is also conveniently archived by date. Since I could use the date as my common variable, I decided to investigate if my mobility was affected by the Covid cases within Texas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction From the academic years of 2000-2002, the University of Texas at Austin collected data to analyze the connection between different course evaluations to the ratings of beauty for its instructors. This dataset includes 12 variables with 463 observations. For the numeric variables, the dataset recorded the age of the instructions as “age”, the averaged rating (in which the mean was set to zero) by a panel of six students of the instructor’s physical appearance as “beauty”, the evaluation score for the course (on a scale of 1-5, meaning low to high) as “eval”, how many students participated in the evaluation as “students”, and the total number of students enrolled in the course as “allstudents”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
